[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Reason for Investing",
		"answer": "Retirement, General Savings, Others: Emergency"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "Annual income",
		"answer": "₦12,000.00"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "Investment Knowledge",
		"answer": "Somewhat familiar"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "When I invest money, my primary goal is to:",
		"answer": "Preserve my investment"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "How much volatility are you comfortable with?",
		"answer": "Moderate. I am willing to take moderate risk as long as my investments have a greater potential for growth over time"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "With respect to your investment goals, which statement best describes your attitude?",
		"answer": "It is important that the value of my investments keep pace with inflation. I am willing to risk an occasional depreciation in value."
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "If the value of your portfolio drops by 20%, what action will you take?",
		"answer": "Sell part of your investment"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "How would you divide your investment?",
		"answer": "30% in Investment A and 70% in Investment B"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "Please select the response that best describes your expected annual rate of return:",
		"answer": "10% to 15%"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "When is the earliest you anticipate needing access to the invested funds?",
		"answer": "Short Term (2 - 5 years)"
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "How much is monthly disposable income available for investing?",
		"answer": "₦1,200.00"
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "If your response to the preceding question is 'Yes', what percentage increase do you anticipate?",
		"answer": "No, 12%"
	}
]
